It's been a week of some change since
and Amanda We Trust came out and your girl is feeling full.
And I gotta tell you, I had an epiphany
when I was doing the screening in Philadelphia.
I realized that I really am supposed to be an educator.
When I was in Philly and we were doing the screening,
people were like, oh, I learned so much.
It just felt like empowering to watch.
And it really felt good to know
that I could do that with my art.
Because sometimes you feel like you have to choose
if you're gonna be like the educator,
hitting them in the head,
or if you're gonna be the one making folks feel good.
So it really makes me feel great
that y'all are feeling good seeing
and Amanda We Trust.
If you have not, and you're here at Patreon,
and Amanda We Trust will be available for another week.
It means so much to me and I'm really proud of myself.